Guide to the Dorothy Schefer Faux fashion collection, 1931-2017.
Faux, Dorothy Schefer fashion collection
- Media, 1967-2001
  - Videos, 1982-2001
    - Fashion Show, Fendi Fall/Winter 1999-2000, Fall-Winter 1999-2000; V-9324 (Box 23)
      Old VID 2
    - Fashion Show, Givenchy Fall/Winter 1999-2000, Fall-Winter 1999-2000; V-9326 (Box 23)
      Old VID 4
    - Fashion Show, Oscar de la Renta Fall 1999, Fall 1999; V-9327 (Box 23)
      Old VID 5
    - Calvin Klein Spring 1998 Collection, Spring 1998; V-9328 (Box 23)
      Old VID 6
    - Chanel Ready-to-Wear Fall/Winter 1993-94, Fall-Winter 1993-1994; V-9329 (Box 23)
      Old VID 7
    - Chanel Couture 1996, 1996; V-9330 (Box 23)
      Old VID 8
    - W Spring 1994 Fashion Show, Spring 1994; V-9331 (Box 23)
      Old VID 9
    - "D" Spring 1997 Runway Show, Spring 1997; V-9335 (Box 23)
      Old VID 30
    - Calvin Klein Spring 1997, Spring 1997; V-9337 (Box 23)
      Old VID 32
    - Calvin Klein Fall 1997, Fall 1997; V-9338 (Box 23)
      Old VID 33
    - Calvin Klein Womens Fall 1996, Fall 1996; V-9339 (Box 23)
      Old VID 34
    - Yves Saint Laurent (YSL) Collection PAP Printemps/ETE 1993, 1993; V-9340 (Box 23)
      Old VID 35
    - Chanel Haut Couture 1996, 1996; V-9341 (Box 23)
      Old VID 36
    - Todd Oldham, Bryon Lars Spring 1994, Spring 1994; V-9343 (Box 23)
      Old VID 38
    - JOOP! Fashion Collection 1992, 1992; V-9344 (Box 23)
      Old VID 39
    - Revlon Fall 1993 Breast Cancer Awareness, 1993; V-9332 (Box 23)
      Old VID 10
    - America's Textile: An Industry Fights Back, 1988; V-9361 (Box 23)
    - Manufactured Fibers: A Technical Video, Fall 1989; V-9362 (Box 23)
    - Denim, Jeans & Cone: 1989 Videotape on Making Denim Fabric, 1989; V-9363 (Box 23)
    - Fabrics and Fibers in Furnishings, 1990; V-9364 (Box 23)
    - The Almanac Story, Undated; V-9365 (Box 23)
    - Beauty Pageants: Bright Lights, Big Business, 1992-1993; V-9336 (Box 23)
      Old VID 31
    - Jean-Paul Gaultier Fragrance, 1992-1997; V-9333 (Box 23)
      Old VID 11
    - Donna Karan at Saks Fifth Avenue, 1992-1993; V-9334 (Box 23)
      Old VID 29
    - Clinique, 1992-1997; V-9342 (Box 23)
      Old VID 37
    - Issey Miyake, 1987; V-9345 (Box 23)
      Old VID 40
    - Marc Jacobs Fall 2000, Fall 2000; V-9346 (Box 23)
      Old VID 41
    - John Bartlett Spring 2000 Men & Women, Spring 2000; V-9347 (Box 23)
      Old VID 42
    - Oscar de la Renta Fall 2000, Fall 2000; V-9348 (Box 23)
      Old VID 43
    - Bottega Veneta Primavera/Estate 2000, 2000; V-9349 (Box 23)
      Old VID 44
    - Oscar de la Renta Spring 2000, Spring 2000; V-9350 (Box 23)
      Old VID 45
    - Bottega Veneta Fall 2000, Fall 2000; V-9351 (Box 23)
      Old VID 46
    - DKNY Fall 2000 Runway Show, Fall 2000; V-9352 (Box 23)
      Old VID 47
    - Michael Kors Fall 2000, Fall 2000; V-9353 (Box 23)
      Old VID 48
    - James Purcell Spring 2000, Spring 2000; V-9354 (Box 23)
      Old VID 49
    - Ralph Lauren Fall 2000 Collection Unedited Version, Fall 2000; V-9355 (Box 23)
      Old VID 50
    - Chanel Pret-a-Porter Fall-Winter 2000/2001, Fall-Winter 2000-2001; V-9356 (Box 23)
      Old VID 51
    - James Purcell Fall 2000, Fall 2000; V-9357 (Box 23)
      Old VID 52
    - Donna Karan Fall 2000 Runway Show, Fall 2000; V-9358 (Box 23)
      Old VID 53
    - Calvin Klein Fall 1999 Women's Collection, Fall 1999; V-9359 (Box 23)
      Old VID 54
    - Calvin Klein Women's Collection Fall 2000, Fall 2000; V-9360 (Box 23)
      Old VID 55
    - Perfect Size 8, Date Unknown; V-9679; Groth, Robin (Box 29)
    - Clinque: What Age Great Skin, Date Unknown; V-9680 (Box 29)
    - The Quiet Revolution, May 11, 1994; V-9681; Yarre Films (Box 29)
    - Prescriptives "Jane" video, August 3, 1993; V-9682 (Box 29)
    - Low Impact Aerobic Workout, 1986; V-9683; Fonda, Jane (Box 29)
    - Calvin Cline Biography, Date Unknown; V-9684; A & E (Box 29)
    - Super Callanetics, 1988; V-9685; Pinckney, Callan (Box 29)
    - Jean Gaultier, Date Unknown; V-9686 (Box 29)
    - Low Impact Aerobic Workout, 1986; V-9687; Fonda, Jane (Box 29)
    - Norma Kamali Beauty, Date Unknown; V-9688 (Box 29)
    - Quick Callanetics: Hips and Behind, 1991; V-9689; Pinckney, Callan (Box 29)
    - Easy Going, 1987; V-9690; Fonda, Jane (Box 29)
    - Canyon Ranch: Mini Maxi Power X 2, 1984; V-9691; Kientzler, Karma (Box 29)
    - Heart Beat Ballet, 1994; V-9692 (Box 29)
    - AM/PM Callanetic, 1992; V-9693; Pinckney, Callan (Box 29)
    - Callanetics, 1986; V-9694; Pinckney, Callan (Box 29)
    - MAC Cosmetics: The First Ten Years, August 22, 1996; V-9695 (Box 29)
    - This is the Body Shop, August 9, 1992; V-9696 (Box 29)
    - The Body Shop #209, June 11, 1993; V-9697 (Box 29)
    - The Famine Within, 1990; V-9698 (Box 29)
      documentary
    - Workout, 1982; V-9699; Fonda, Jane (Box 29)
    - House of Style: A Model Conversation, Date Unknown; V-9700 (Box 29)
    - Body Shop International - "Trade Not Aid Rock Promo", Date Unknown; V-9701; Jacaranda productions (Box 29)
    - Dance Away the Fifties, 1987; V-9702; Fox, Molly (Box 29)
    - Dance Away the Sixties, 1987; V-9703; Fox, Molly (Box 29)
    - Picture What Women Do, Date Unknown; V-9704; Lifetime television (Box 29)
    - Frontliners Image of Women, September 1995; V-9705 (Box 29)
    - Viva Glam "Salute to Suburbia", July 1995; V-9706; MAC cosmetics (Box 29)
    - Retailing in the 90's: The Demographic Revolution, Spring-Summer 1994; V-9707; Harper's Bazaar (Box 29)
      Trends breakfast
    - Canyon Ranch: Body Contouring, 1984; V-9708; Kientzler, Karma (Box 29)
    - In the Round in Your Face, 1989; V-9822; Def Leppard; Polygram music video (Box 30)
    - Vulgar Video, 1993; V-9823; Pantera; A Vision Entertainment (Box 30)
    - Attack of the Killer Bees, 1991; V-9824; Anthrax; Island Visual Arts (Box 30)
    - Uncensored, 1986; V-9825; Motley Crue; Elektra Entertainment (Box 30)
    - Unplugged, Date Unknown; V-9826; Denis Leary (Box 30)
      not commercially made
    - Didivnikufesin N.F.V., 1987-11-16; V-9827; Anthrax; Island Visual Arts (Box 30)
    - A New Men's Fragrance is Coming, Date Unknown; V-9828; Cosmair (Box 30)
    - Lancome Bienfait Total Personal Cleansing Duo Rev. 2, Date Unknown; V-9829; Cosmair (Box 30)
    - Calvin Klein on Escape, Date Unknown; V-9830; Calvin Klein Cosmetics; Kenwood Group (Box 30)
    - Anna Wintour Interview, 1988-12-18; V-9831; Today Show; Conde Nast Inc. (Box 30)
    - Eternity/Eternity for Men, 1991; V-9832; Calvin Klein; LRP video (Box 30)
    - Fox on Trends, 1997-06-18; V-9833 (Box 30)
    - Coco, The Spirit of Chanel, 1992; V-9834 (Box 30)
    - Awake, Kissed, Explore Dangerous, 1990-09-26; V-9835; Calvin Klein; LRP video (Box 30)
    - Colors by Yves Saint Laurent, Date Unknown; V-9836; Yves Saint Laurent (Box 30)
    - Who is Egoste, 1991-08-13; V-9837; Chanel; Reilly Video Communications (Box 30)
    - No title, Date Unknown; V-9838; Chanel (Box 30)
    - 1994-1995 Fall Winter Ready to Wear, 1994-03-28; V-9839; Chanel; Devlin videoservice (Box 30)
    - Chanel Collection PAP 1995-1996, 1995-05-10; V-9840; Chanel; Devlin videoservice (Box 30)
    - Eternity, Date Unknown; V-9841; Calvin Klein; Mediatech East (Box 30)
      12 spots
    - White Diamonds, 1991-06-18; V-9842; Elizabeth Arden; Post Expressions (Box 30)
    - Calvin Klein Cosmetics Escape, 1991; V-9843; Clavin Klein; LRP Video (Box 30)
    - Chanel No. 5, 1991-10-09; V-9844; Chanel; Reilly Video Communications (Box 30)
    - Calvin Klein Obsession, 1989-05-02; V-9845; Calvin Klein; Mediatech East (Box 30)
    - Maschino New York Party, Date Unknown; V-9846 (Box 30)
    - Princess Marcella Borghese, 1994; V-9847; Madoff (Box 30)
    - Women and Their Shoes and the Men Who Hate Them, show #1-05, Date Unknown; V-9848; Bertice Berry Show (Box 30)
      master copy
    - Red My Lips, Date Unknown; V-9849; Estee Lauder (Box 30)
    - Picture What Women Do, 1994; V-9850; Lifetime Television (Box 30)
      Public service campaign
    - Global Style Network, 1998-07-30; V-9851; Second Coming Producations (Box 30)
    - Estee Lauder: Sweet Smell of Success, 1999; V-9852; A&E Entertainment (Box 30)
    - Larry King Live, 1993-04-12; V-9853 (Box 30)
    - The Dinzel's Tango! A Master Class, 1986; V-9854; American Show Brokers (Box 30)
    - The Fourth Annual Rainforest Benefit Concert, 1992-03-18; V-9855; Iceberg Rainforest Foundation; Centerlight Television (Box 30)
    - Lucy Awards Highlights, 1999; V-9856; Hollywood Target Promotion and Marketing (Box 30)
    - This is the Body Shop, 1993-07-08; V-9857; The Body Shop; PDR Productions (Box 30)
    - Trade Not Aid Rock Promo, 1993-06-29; V-9858; The Body Shop; PDR Productions (Box 30)
    - You Will, Date Unknown; V-9859; AT&T; Audio Visual Support Group (Box 30)
      AT&T brand campaign
    - Bitch Magazine, 1994-02-1994-03
  - Tape Recordings, Undated
    - Budget Standards-Seminar Speakers, Undated; TR-10934 (Box 23)
      Reel-to-reels
    - Symbolism in Occupational Dress - Question and Answer Period, Undated; TR-10935 (Box 23)
    - Family Expenditure For Clothing, Undated; TR-10936 (Box 23)
  - Records, 1967-1984
    - "Give Me Time"/ "The Look of Love", 1967; SR-15345; Springfield, Dusty; Philips (Box 25)
      45 rpm records
    - "The Beginning of Loneliness"/ "Alfie", 1967; SR-15346; Warwick, Dionne; Scepter Records (Box 25)
    - "The All American Boy"/ "Rubber Dolly", Undated; SR-15347; Parsons, Bill; Collectable Record Corp. (Box 25)
      Reissue
    - "Do They Know It's Christmas?"/ "Feed the World", 1984; SR-15348-SR-15349; Band Aid; Columbia (Box 25)
      Two copies